Thomas S. Power Papers
Thomas S. Power Papers
- Audiovisual material
  - Tapes
    - Washington Report of the Air, for July 21 - July 25, 1969; power_ts_0072; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For July 21 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Southeast Asians Face Red Realities; Tape 2, For July 22 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Mboya’s Assassination in Kenya; Tape 3, For July 23 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - World Communists Rubber-stamp Kremlin Authority; Tape 4, For July 24 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Nixon and Rumania; Tape 5, For July 25 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Asian Mutual Security Pact Urged. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for July 28 - August 1, 1969; power_ts_0073; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For July 28 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Letter from a Soviet Concentration Camp; Tape 2, For July 29 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Latin America in Revolt; Tape 3, For July 30 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - New Iraq Assault on Kurds; Tape 4, For July 31 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Reds and West German Elections; Tape 5, For August 1 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Westerner Sees China’s Nuclear Arsenal. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for August 4 - August 8, 1969; power_ts_0074; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For August 4 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - A New Era, New Realities for Soviets; Tape 2, For August 5 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Russian Fleet in the Atlantic; Tape 3, For August 6 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - United States and Israel Scored by Reds in the Mideast; Tape 4, For August 7 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - "Soccer War," A Red Gain; Tape 5, For August 8 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Artillery and the Soviet Military Industrial Complex. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for August 11 - August 15, 1969; power_ts_0075; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For August 11 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - No Coalition For Giang Dang Survivors; Tape 2, For August 12 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Soviet Maneuvers To Suppress Czechoslovakians; Tape 3, For August 13 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Hoover’s Report: The Enemy Within; Tape 4, For August 14 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Latin American Subversion Renewed; Tape 5, For August 15 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - South Africa’s Appeal to the West. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for August 18 - August 22, 1969; power_ts_0076; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For August 18 (Monday) - Blueprint for Hemisphere Revolution Released - Dr. Walter H. Judd; Tape 2, For August 19 (Tuesday) - Russian Writer Kuznetsov Defects - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis; Tape 3, For August 20 (Wednesday) - Kuznetsov: From Shadows of Fear - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis; Tape 4, For August 21 (Thursday) - British Problems with a Defector - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis; Tape 5, For August 22 (Friday) - Story of an African Revolutionary - Dr. Walter H. Judd. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for August 25 - August 29, 1969; power_ts_0077; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For August 25 (Monday) - Micronesia: America’s "Bali Hai" - Dr. Walter H. Judd; Tape 2, For August 26 (Tuesday) - The New Soviet Strategy In Asia - Dr. Walter H. Judd; Tape 3, For August 27 (Wednesday) - Russian Control Of Intellectual Minds - John F. Lewis; Tape 4, For August 28 (Thursday) - Dean Acheson’s Assessment of The Red Threat - Dr. Walter H. Judd; Tape 5, For August 29 (Friday) - The Soviet Union As It Really Is - Dr. Walter H. Judd. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for Sept. 1 - Sept. 5, 1969; power_ts_0078; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For Sept. 1 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - How Peking Builds Support for Subversion; Tape 2, For Sept. 2 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Peking Support for Latin American Terrorists; Tape 3, For Sept. 3 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Communist Gain, Central America’s Loss; Tape 4, For Sept. 4 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Red Complaints, Whose Ox Is Gored?; Tape 5, For Sept. 5 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Clarification of Soviet Missile Developments. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for September 8 - September 12, 1969; power_ts_0079; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For September 8 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Communism’s Latest Assault on Czechoslovakia; Tape 2, For September 9 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - South Africa’s Naval Importance; Tape 3, For September 10 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - French Aid to South Africa’s Defenses; Tape 4, For September 11 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Red China Bolsters Its Soviet Frontier; Tape 5, For September 12 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - A Tourist’s Nightmare in Russia. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for September 15 - September 19, 1969; power_ts_0080; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For September 15 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - The Demise of a Pro-Western Libya; Tape 2, For September 16 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet-Spanish Port Agreement; Tape 3, For September 17 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Zambia: Example of Bad Red Advice; Tape 4, For September 18 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Reds Cooperate to Destroy; Tape 5, For September 19 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Kremlin Complaint About West’s Propaganda. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
Selected index to correspondence
Adams, Paul D. 1961 Dec 6 1963 Jun 11
Aiken, George D. 1960 May 3
Allen, William M. 1957 Jul 10 1961 Jan 17 1961 Feb 2 1961 Mar 31 1961 Sep 29 1964 Nov 23
Alsop, Joseph 1959 Mar 5
Beall, J. Glenn 1957 Feb 27
Beerman, Ralph F. 1964 Dec 4
Bergan, G.T. 1964 Feb 24 1964 Apr 14 1968 Jan 3
Boggs, J. Caleb 1965 Jul 7
Bolton, Frances P. 1962 Aug 13
Bradley, Mark E. Jr. 1950 Feb 23 1963 May 28
Brewster, Daniel B. 1964 Mar 18 1964 Mar 26
Bridges, Styles 1960 Mar 2
Brundage, Percival 1964 Dec 3
Bryant, Farris 1963 Dec 31
Buckley, William F. 1969 Apr 30 1969 Jun 17
Burke, Arleigh 1961 Apr 19
Callaway, Lew L. 1964 Feb 17
Cannon, Howard W. 1963 Jun 11
Case, Francis 1959 Nov 20
Childlaw, B. W. 1954 Mar 23
Clark, Mark W. 1963 Sep 25
Clay, Lucius D. 1962 Feb 5 1963 Dec 4 1964 Nov 23 1967 Jan 1967 Oct 6
Collbohm, Frariol 1962 Jan 5 1962 Mar 14 1963 Apr 30 1964 Jul 20
Considine, Bob 1963 Dec 23
Cousins, Norman 1963 Sep 18
Craigie, L. C. 1952 Jul 28 1957 May 20 1963 Oct 25 1964 Gen
Curtis, Carl T. 1960 Sep 12 1963 Oct 8 1963 Nov 5
Daniel, Price 1959 Nov 10
Davis, Frank W. 1961 Jan 13 1961 May 26 1961 Jul 13 1961 Aug 28 1961 Sep 14 1964 Jan 7
Dole, Robert 1964 Jan 4
Dominick, Peter H. 1970 Sep 16
Donovan, Hedley 1964 Apr 27
Douglas, Donald W. 1958 Aug 22 1958 Sep 12 1960 Aug 8
Dulles, Allen 1954 Jan 11
Faker, Ira C. 1960 May 6 1961 Oct 30 1962 Mar 14 1964 Dec 2 1965 Mar 24 1968 Mar 20
Ellsworth, Robert 1967 May 1
Foss, Joe 1957 Aug 28 1957 Sep 10 1957 Oct 3 1958 Nov 12 1962 Apr 17
Fulbright, J. William 1960 Jan 26
Godfrey, Arthur 1958 Jan 9 1959 May 25 1959 Sep 1
Goldwater, Barry 1961 Jun 14 1964 Jan 21 1968 Aug 15
Hagerty, James C. 1962 May 17
Halleck, Charles A. 1960 Oct 7
Hardin, Clifford M. 1963 Sep 30
Hart, Philip A. 1966 Jan 18
Hickenlooper, Bourke B. 1950 May 22
Hollings, Ernest F. 1959 Sep 15
Hope, Bob 1962 Mar 27
Hopper, Hedda 1959 Sep 10 1960 Aug 17
Hosmer, Craig 1963 Aug 30
Hruska, Roman L. 1953 Nov 20 1957 Dec 11 1957 Dec 13 1958 Jan 14 1961 Mar 16 1962 May 21
Johnson, G.K. 1963 Mar 19
Johnson, U. Alexis 1961 Jul 17 1961 Jul 18
Kalber, Floyd 1964 Apr 29
Kennedy, John F. 1962 Apr 3
Kennedy, Robert F. 1964 Apr 25
Kinter, William R. 1968 Jan 19 1968 Aug 7 1969 Dec 3 1970 Sep 4
Kissinger, Henry A. 1960 Mar 9
Duter, Laurence S. 1955 May 11 1957 May 14 1957 May 21 1959 May 28 1961 May 5
LeMay, Curtis E. 1954 Oct 14 1957 Apr 13 1957 Nov 23 1961 May 29 1966 Oct 6 1966 Oct 11 1967 Mar 13 1967 May 10
Lemnitzer, L. 1961 Aug 31 1962 Jun 18 1962 Sep 20
Lewis, Roger 1965 Feb 2 1965 Apr 6 1965 May 3
Lincoln, Frank B. 1967 Jul 14 1967 Jul 24 1967 Oct 4 1967 Nov 22 1968 Feb 8 1968 Feb 19 1968 Mar 26 1968 Jul 16 1968 Jul 30 1968 Sep 11 1968 Nov 9
Ling, James L. 1963 Jun 7
Lindsay, Richard C. 1948 Dec 29 1951 Oct 24
Lodge, Henry Cabot 1958 Apr 28
Long, Russell B. 1952 Aug 7
McCone, John A. 1950 Dec 27 1967 Sep 7
McConnell, J. P. 1958 Dec 24 1961 Jun 1965 Feb 2 1967 Mar 1967 Oct 18
McElroy, Neil 1958 Apr 26
MacGregor, Clark 1970 Aug 14
McNamara, Robert S. 1961 Sep 1 1962 Feb 27 1963 Jan 31 1963 Jan 19 1963 Jul 1
Miller, Troup Jr. 1961 Oct 3 1962 May 8 1962 Jan 2
Montgomery, Field Marshal the Viscount of Alamein 1965 Jun 5
Morrison, Frank B. 1961 May 22 1964 Apr 30
Murphy, George 1968 Jun 11 1969 Dec 13
Nimitz, Chester 1965 Mar 27
Nixon, Richard M. 1967 Feb 9 1967 Oct 26 1968 Jan 5 1968 Apr 8 1968 Apr 16 1968 May 25 1968 Jun 28 1968 Jul 29 1968 Aug 1 1968 Aug 26 1969 Jan 14
Nixon, Richard M. [C. Calvert Knudsen, Office of the President-Elect] 1968 Dec 2
Norstad, Lauris 1952 Aug 13 1957 Oct 15
Old, Archie J. Jr. 1957 Jun 19 1958 Dec 12 1960 Jun 18 1961 Mar 15 1962 Sep 7 1963 Feb 25
Pace, Frank Jr. 1957 May 21 1958 Nov 12 1959 Jan 22 1959 Oct 26 1960 Dec 6 1963 Oct 15 1964 Nov 24 1965 Feb 15 1965 Mar 23
Quarles, Donald A. 1955 Jan 4 1957 Apr 8
Ransom, Harry Howe 1960 Mar 14
Rawlings, E. W. 1956 Jul 30 1959 Feb 10
Reagan, Ronald 1967 May 23 1968 Aug 19
Reynolds, Sam W. 1954 Jul 23
Rivers, L. Mendel 1967 Aug 16
Rumsfeld, Donald 1963 Aug 12
Rusk, Dean 1963 Apr 6
Russell, Richard B. 1961 Mar 7
Ryan, John D. 1952 Oct 10 1957 May 22 1962 Nov 14 1964 Dec 23 1965 Feb 18 1969 Dec 3
Schlafly, J. Fred 1967 Oct 18 1968 Mar 11 1968 Apr 10 1968 Apr 4 1968 Aug 19 1968 Aug 21
Schlafly, Phyliss 1966 Feb 7 1966 May 16 1966 Jun 23 1966 Aug 8 1968 Mar 28 1968 Aug 21
Schlatter, D. M. 1948 Nov 17 1948 Dec 23 1950 Jan 20 1953 Mar 5 1953 Sep 28 1955 Aug 2 1956 Mar 15 1957 May 21 1965 Feb
Schriever, B. A. 1955 Feb 3 1957 Nov 6 1962 Aug 27
Smart, Jacob E. 1964 Feb 13
Spaatz, Carl A. 1961 Mar 30 1964 Nov 17
Spellman, Francis Cardinal 1964 Jul 6 1965 Feb 25
Spivak, Lawrence E. 1957 May 21 1964 Apr 17 1964 Nov 30 1965 Jan 8 1965 Mar 23
Stennis, John 1962 Jun 19
Stewart, James 1963 Dec 2
Stikker, D. U. 1963 Jun 4
Stratemeyer, George E. 1963 Aug 21
Stratton, Samuel F. 1960 Feb 17
Sweeney, W. C. Jr. 1958 Dec 30 1959 Sep 29
Swofford, R. P. Jr. 1955 Sep 6 1964 Nov 13
Sylvester, Arthur 1961 May 23 1961 Jun 7
Symington, Stuart 1951 Dec 29 1954 Jan 5 1954 Jan 18 1954 Aug 9 1957 May 24 1961 Jan 7 1964 Oct 19
Taylor, Maxwell 1962 Dec 7
Thomas, Lowell 1959 Sep 10 1959 Oct 1
Todt, George 1964 Nov 29 1965 Mar 1 1965 Mar 7 1965 Mar 8 1966 Jan 14 1970 Aug 8
Truman, Harry S. 1959 Aug 3
Tunney, Gene 1960 Jan 22 1960 Feb 12 1960 Mar 18
Twining, Nathan F. 1954 Jun 16 1956 Jul 18 1958 Apr 10 1968 Jun 4
Vandenberg, Hoyt S. 1949 Jun 14
Vinson, Carl 1964 Jul 24
Wallace, Dewitt 1957 Oct 18 1959 Dec 30 1964 Mar 30
Watson, Thomas J. Jr. 1956 Feb 9 1956 Jun 8 1957 May 22
Wedemeyer, A.C. 1963 Aug 22
Westmoreland, W.C. 1960 Aug 25
Weyland, O.P. 1955 Jun 15 1957 Jun 4
Wheeler, Earle G. 1964 Sep 23
Wheless, Hewitt T. 1965 Feb 4 1967 Sep 11
Wilson, C.E. 1954 May 17
White, Thomas D. 1951 Aug 27 1953 May 27 1957 Apr 11 1957 Sep 17 1958 Jul 7 1959 Dec 7 1960 Aug 25 1961 Aug 17 1962 May 31 1963 May 17 1963 May 19 1963 Aug 15 1965 Feb 18 1965 Mar 8
Williams, Robert H. 1963 Sep 16
Wright, Jerauld 1958 Sep 6 1963 Jan 14
Wyman, Louis C. 1963 Aug 21
Yorty, Sam 1964 Nov 9 1969 Dec 1
Zuckert, Eugene M. 1952 Nov 6 1964 Nov 24